V游网字幕组荣誉出品  如有不当之处还请见谅
感谢翻译者 叮,spawnix,vootoo
最新大片下载尽在www.verypsp.com
坚持，坚持，别挂啊
Hang on, hang on. Come on.
查理，你在哪儿？还有，我的钱呢？
Where are you, Charlie? More importantly, where is my money?
你欠我3万 杰克，我会还你的
- You're into me for 30 grand. - Jack, I'm going to pay you.
我不是 Jack，是Bill Panner.
This ain't Jack! Lt's Bill Panner.
你还欠 Jack钱？先还我的
You owe Jack money, too? You pay me first!
Bill，我们是好兄弟，我正准备还你，马上就还
Bill. We're good, buddy. I got your money. It's right here in my hand.
要不在$&*%见面！##￥@￥
Why don't we meet up on the?
你电话效果不好，喂？ 我听不见
- Your phone's going all screwy. Hello? - I'm losing you.
我听不清你在说什么
I can't hear what you're say...
请问那是Ambush么？
Hey, mister. Is that Ambush?
是的 能见见他么？
- Yeah. - Can we see him?
你们想见他？ 是的
- You want to see him? - Yeah.
等会儿
Give me a minute.
这
This...
就是Ambush，醒醒，醒醒
...is Ambush. Wakey, wakey.
它要和什么机器人打？ 事实上它要打……
- What robot is he fighting? - Actually he's going to fight...
等等，小美女，你们想干什么？
Whoa, little lady. What are you doing?
可以跟他合照吗？
Can we get a picture with him?
当然，5块钱
Sure. For five dollars.
5块钱？开玩笑的吧
You want five dollars? Seriously?
没有，我现在就要5块钱
No, I want five dollars immediately.
走吧
Come on, guys.
好啦，我开玩笑的，3块钱      表！
- All right, I'm kidding. Three bucks. - Whatever.
两块五怎么样？ 去死吧
- How about $2.50? - You suck!
又要去那些个小镇上了
It's going to be one of those towns, huh?
女士们先生们，欢迎来到2020圣莱昂德罗
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to the 2020 San Leandro County Fair.
请坐好，表演即将开始
Please take your seats. We're almost ready to get this thing started.
听说我的机器人要对抗800磅的家伙
I was told my bot was fighting an 800-pound steer.
那个不是800磅，蠢蛋
That is not 800 pounds, knucklehead.
Charlie，“无所不能”Kenton。混得不怎么样嘛，伙计
Charlie "the Can Do Kid" Kenton. Time has not been good to you, my friend.
Ricky，我们有大麻烦了 慢点说，慢点说，hoss.
- ,we got a big problem here. - Slow down there, hoss.
上次见到你是在休斯顿中心，你还被我的铁臂金刚揍得
Last time I saw you, you were staring at the ceiling at the Sam Houston Center
找不着北呢
with the taste of my right cross all over your face.
我们来这儿没问题吗 没有
- Are we good to go here? - Yeah.
我们压了3000块同意让我们的拳击手对抗800磅的家伙
We agreed that my boxer would fight an 800-pound steer for three grand.
对吧？ 是的，是这样的
- Am I right? - Yes, sir. We did.
但那家伙看上去有2000磅
That bull is like 2,000 pounds.
听好了
I'll tell you something.
要是你的机器人不打我们就不付钱！怎么样
Your bot don't fight, you don't get paid! How about that?
滚出去
Get the hell out of here.
要不来点有趣的，我的机器人对抗你的牛，爽快点
Why don't we make this more interesting. My bot against your bull, straight up.
出多少 2万，胜者为王
- How much? - Twenty grand, winner takes all.
2万？你有的起？ 在我卡车的保险箱里
- Twenty grand. You got 20 grand? - In a safe in my truck.
好的，Charlie
All right, Charlie.
就2万，但要是你输了
Twenty grand it is, but if you lose and you welch,
我会跟着你，揍你直到天涯海角
I'll come after you and beat you to within an inch of your life.
你知道我说得出就做得到
You know that I can do that because I already done done it!
平常你是紧追不舍的，比赛的时候就怂了
In life you get too close, in the ring you stand back like a girl. Just shake.
好，像上次那样？你想再跳一次舞吗？
All right. Shake and pow! Just like that once again. You want to dance again?
为他欢呼吧，祝他好运，他需要些狗屎运
Cheer for this guy. Give him some luck. He needs some luck, y'all.
别摸那牛
Don't touch that bull.
女士们，先生们，我要问问
Ladies and gentlemen, I got to ask,
在场的有多少喜欢机器人格斗？
do we have any fans of robot boxing here today?
朋友们，我懂
Now, listen, friends, I understand
我们不可能去Dallas
we can't all afford to go all the way over there to Dallas
花300块看机器人拳击联盟比赛
and pay $300 for one of those World Robot Boxing League fights.
所以今天我决定把机器人拳击带到这儿
So, I decided that I would bring a robot boxing match
带到 San Leandro
right here to our little fair here in San Leandro.
怎么样？
How about that?
女士们，先生们，向您介绍
Ladies and gentlemen, I introduce to you,
Ambush!
上吧！
Let's do it!
好了，大家伙
All right, big fella.
真是个大家伙，是吧
He's a big fella, ain't he?
转过来，让他们看看你有多漂漂
Take a turn. Let them see how beautiful you are.
秀一下
Show them some power.
看看，他在表演功夫
Look at that. He's getting all kung fu-y on us.
大家伙
Yeah, big fella.
Ambush!今天的对手是去年
Ambush's opponent today, he's last year's runner-up
公牛比赛的亚军
in the baddest of the bulls competition,
女士们先生，来欢迎
ladies and gentlemen,
Black Thunder!
让它上场 开始吧
- Let's get it on! - Let's get this thing started.
你就这点本事？
Is that all you got?
来吧，伙计
Yeah, brother. Bring it on.
抓住它，抓住它
Take him, take him.
Ambush用上了攻击波
Ambush lays the smackdown on that prime beef.
好戏才刚刚开始呢
I got more for you, big fella. We're just getting started.
好了，跳，现在
OK. Jump, now!
Ambush，打倒Black Thunde
Ambush, decks Black Thunder,
你和牛厮打的时候要小心咯
but when you mess with the bull, you're going to get the horns.
你喜欢这样，我看出来了
You like that. I can tell. You like that.
转身
Turn around!
Ricky， Ricky快让它停下
Ricky! Ricky, stop this thing!
挺住啊，我们还在比赛，跳，跳
Come on. We're still in this thing. Just hop. Hop.
就这样，挺住
That's it. Come on.
Ricky，够了，够了！
Ricky, enough! Enough!
我听不见你的机器人被毁了
I can't hear you over the sound of your robot being destroyed.
毁了他！毁了他！
Kill! Kill! Kill!
加油，起来啊
Come on, get up.
起来，快啊
Get up! Come on!
不
No!
别这样，不，不，不，不！
Come on, no. No, no, no!
女士们先生们，让我们听听这声音
Ladies and gentlemen, let's hear it for our warriors out here today
我们的战士在2020莱安德罗被终结了
at the 2020 San Leandro County Fair.
谢谢观赏
Thank you for coming out,
下次见，还会再继续的
and we'll see you next time, because there will be one.
把腿给我
Give me that leg.
好啊，给我5块钱
Sure. For five dollars.
Boo-yah!
好了，女士们先生们，这是不是很有趣呢
All right! That was ridonculous fun, now wasn't it, ladies and gentlemen?
我一会儿找你拿钱， Charlie，你最好真有钱
I'm going to come by for my money, Charlie boy. You best have it.
大家一起说“嘿” 嘿
- Everybody say "hey!" - Hey!
一起说“HO”
- Everybody say "ho!" - Ho!
来看这个，你还好吧，机器小伙？
How about that? How you doing there, little robot?
钥匙拿不出来了，可恶
My keys, damn it.
再上前一步我就把你像你的基友一样揍倒
One more step and I'll drop you like your girlfriend.
Charlie，别紧张
Charlie, relax.
我不会给你钱的，这是打假赛，我机器人都被毁了
I'm not paying you. That was a bogus fight. It cost me my last robot.
听我们说 还记得Caroline Fallon吗？
- Just listen to us. - Do you recall Caroline Fallon?
我前女友，十年没见了，她想干嘛？
She's my ex-girlfriend. I haven't seen her in ten years. What does she want?
没有，她死了
Nothing. She died.
记得马 Max Kenton?
Do you recall Max Kenton?
我儿子，快九岁了
He's my son. He's got to be nine.
11岁 11岁，好吧
- Eleven. - Eleven. OK.
也死了？
Is he dead, too?
不，他很好，所以我们才来这
No, he's fine. That's why we're here.
法庭宣布了孩子的监护状况
This court is convened to address the custodial status
Max Kenton? 11岁
of one Max Kenton, age 11.
母亲Caroline Fallon已故，父亲Charles Kenton.
Mother, Caroline Fallon, deceased. Father, Charles Kenton.
Debra Fallon Barnes，你是孩子的婶婶
Debra Fallon Barnes, you're the boy's aunt.
是的，之前我也说过我丈夫Marvin挺富裕
Yes. As I've already told you, my husband, Marvin, is wealthy,
我们能够好好照顾 Max
and we can more than provide for Max.
感谢您的好意，但是根据德克萨斯州法，
I appreciate that, but per Texas state law, without a written will
没有亲属托管的书面意愿书是不可以的
next of kin retains custody.
Charles Kenton，他知道这次听证会
Charles Kenton, who is aware of this custody hearing,
我们希望他
and we are expecting him...
我需要个新的机器人
I need a new robot now.
下周六 Ambush要大干一场
I had a big fight for Ambush next Saturday.
我得秀点什么
I got to show up with something.
Noisy Boy打折？这段时间，吵闹男孩太要命了
Noisy Boy is for sale? In his day, Noisy Boy was a killer.
多少钱？不错啊，有什么毛病
How much? That's a good deal. What's wrong with him?
这个可以接受
I can live with that.
我没有
I don't have it.
Charles Kenton在孩子出生后就没有履行他的监护义务
Charles Kenton waived all of his rights to custody right after the boy was born.
我可以做的比他更好
I can more than provide for Max.
你就是Charles Kenton吧
Please be Charles Kenton.
Charlie.，是的，是我
Charlie, yeah.
我是来签什么权转让书的
I'm here to sign some paper that releases my rights
我儿子的监护权
to the custody of my son.
所以我就来了，需要我来吗？
That's why I'm here. Do I need to be here?
Charlie.
还记得我吗？
Do you even remember me?
Debra，Caroline的姐姐 是的， Debra，你还好吗？
- Debra, Caroline's sister. - Yeah, Debra. How are you?
Kenton先生请坐
Mr. Kenton. Please take a seat.
请问我现在可以见见我的侄子吗？
Your Honor, may I please go and see my nephew now?
可以
Yes, you may.
那您呢?Kenton先生 什么？
- How about you, Mr. Kenton? - What?
要是您愿意的话，您可以和他呆会儿
You can spend some time with him, if you'd like.
和孩子? 是的
- With the kid? - Yeah, the kid.
Max，他还是你儿子吗？ 好吧
- Max. Your son? - All right.
一天就搞什么机器人，你自己就是机器人
You've been working with those robots for so long, you've become one.
亲爱的，你在这儿等等，我一会儿就来
Honey, you wait right here. I'm going to be back.
没事儿，多久都可以，甜心
You take all the time you need, sweetheart.
阁下，如果可以的话，这种时候
Your Honor, I'd like to, at this juncture,
我想叫我的律师过来
step out and call my attorney, if that's all right.
可以
Please.
快点，快点，来了
Come on. Come on. There you are.
他会被收养
He'll be in a foster home.
他们会给他找个好人家的，是的，年轻，有活力
No, they find good families. Young. Energetic. Yeah.
谢了， Michael，我会的
Thanks, Michael. I will. OK.
我是Marvin Barnes， Debra的丈夫 对，是的
- Marvin Barnes. I'm Debra's husband. - Right, yeah.
Debra真的很想收养 Max
Debra really wants to adopt Max.
我也很赞成，但是 7万5
- I'm up for it. But... - Seventy-five grand.
7万5？你在开玩笑吧
$75,000? You're serious?
事实上
The thing is...
这个夏天我们要和老朋友还有他妻子去意大利
...we're supposed to go to Italy this summer
最新大片下载尽在www.verypsp.com
在 Tuscany呆两个月
Two months in Tuscany and all over.
就你们四个，真不错
Just the four of you. Sounds nice.
我们八月底会回到纽约
We'll be back in New York by the end of August.
八月，那就10万
In August. A hundred.
10万？ 没错
- $100,000? - You heard me.
你疯了吧 你妻子会更疯
- You're crazy. - Not nearly as crazy as your wife
要是你告诉她我签字把孩子交到德克萨斯
if you tell her I just signed over that kid to the state of Texas.
有一个方法大家都皆大欢喜
There's a real way everyone gets what they want here.
接下来就是你要做的
So here's what you're going to do.
告诉你妻子我把监护权交给她了
You're going to tell your wife I'll only sign over custody to her
要是我先和孩子过完夏天
if I get to spend the summer with the kid first.
就告诉她
Just tell her how guilty she made me feel
让我当个坏爸爸真的很愧疚
for being such a terrible absentee dad,
我多想和他好好相处，尽一个做父亲的义务
how I want to make good with junior, a little fatherly bonding, whatnot.
这样她肯定很高兴，你也当了英雄，就皆大欢喜咯
She'll buy it, you get to be the hero and everybody wins.
不要和Debra提钱的事，懂吗？
OK. But not a word about the money to Debra, you understand?
明白
I understand.
送走Max后我会先给你5万
I'll give you 50 grand tonight when we drop off Max
八月份回来的时候
and the other 50 when we get back in August
你把他送到纽约我们那，我再给你5万
and you deliver him to us in New York.
很高兴与你合作
Pleasure doing business with you.
真高兴大家都抓紧时间办事
Your Honor, I'm happy we all took the time
大家都各得其所
to make the best decision for everyone.
高兴吧？ 是我
- Happy? - Yeah, it's me.
我要 Noisy Boy，我有钱了
I'm buying Noisy Boy. I got the money.
把它带去Tallet体育馆，到那会合
Take him to Tallet's Gym and I'll meet you there.
有人吗？
Hello?
Bailey你在吗？
Bailey?
和你要买的机器人在这
Some guy is here with the robot you're buying,
闻上去真糟糕
and it smells like disaster to me.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you, too.
忘记说了，你今天真可爱 算了吧
- Might I also say how cute you look. - Give it up.
天，我得去洗澡。你要洗吗？来吧
God, I need a shower. You want to take a shower? Come on.
先让我搞清楚
Let me make something clear.
一个恐怖的家伙带着装机器人的箱子
A creepy dude with a robot in a box
在我的体育馆外面坐了俩小时
has been sitting outside my gym for two hours.
先不管是什么情况
Putting aside the fact that you're doing
我猜是你在我家门口做黑交易
what I'm guessing is a black market deal on my doorstep,
Ambush才毁了你怎么付账？
how will you pay him when Ambush just got destroyed?
钱快到了，引开他
The money is on its way. Just distract him.
我一直在，都累死了
I have been. It's exhausting.
你最好了 是吗？真的吗？
- You're the best. - Yeah? Really?
所以你还欠着我6千块就买个4万5的机器人？
Is that why you're buying a $45,000 robot when you owe me six grand in rent?
就因为我人好？ 3千
- Because I'm the best? - Three.
6千。有个有钱人想买这里
Six. There is a guy with real money who wants to buy this place.
切，你才不会卖了你爸爸的体育馆
Come on. Like you're really going to sell your dad's gym.
要是你不租的话我就不能付账，我别无选择
If you don't make rent, I can't make payments and I won't have a choice.
要是你卖了这的话你爹会从坟墓里爬出来揍你的
Your father would climb out of his grave and kick your ass
我爸会爬出来揍你
- if you sold this place. - My father would climb out of his grave
and kick your ass.
Bailey
Bailey?
别 别什么？
- Don't. - Don't what?
别那样做
Don't do that.
别什么 别那样做
- Don't what? - Don't do that thing.
你喜欢那样 不
- No, you like that thing. - No.
你喜欢 我不喜欢
- Yeah. - No, I don't like that thing.
我以前喜欢，但我现在更喜欢钱
I used to. Once. Briefly. Now I like money more.
我不信 管你信不信
- I don't believe you. - I don't care.
Marvin.
钱到了
Your money has arrived.
Marv.
说好的，5万
Fifty grand, as promised.
这是我们在欧洲会用到的号码和联系方式
Here are all our numbers and contact info over in Europe.
都在这了
So that's everything there.
Marvin跟我说这段时间你想跟Max呆一起
So Marvin tells me you want this time with Max.
是的 监护权交给我是正确的选择
- Yeah. - You did the right thing,
giving me custody.
Caroline也会高兴的
Caroline would have wanted that.
八月二十七号把他送来纽约
Now, have him back in New York on August 27th.
没问题
That's a deal.
去接Max吧 走吧，接Max去
OK, let's go get Max. OK? Let's get Max.
你要是想去转转我去接Max也行
It's OK. You want to go around the other side here and I'll get Max?
嗨，Max，回头见
Hey. Max. See you, pal.
宝贝儿，夏天结束见
Max, we'll see you at the end of the summer, honey.
我是Charlie
I'm Charlie.
好久不见了，我是你的……
It's been a long time. You know, I'm your...
你毁了我 说得好
- You screwed me. - Nice mouth.
你知道他们要去哪儿吗？
Do you know where they're going?
意大利？ 对，意大利
- Italy? - Yeah, Italy.
我怎么跟你呆在这？
So how did I get stuck here with you?
别担心，孩子，美好生活还长着呢
Relax, kid. You got a whole life of fine living ahead of you.
Charlie!
那家伙生气了，他要走了
Dude's pissed. He's going to take off.
是Marvin给你的钱吗？ 给，交易结束
- Did Marvin give you that money? - Here, just close the deal.
我一会儿过去
I'll be right there, OK?
我是Bailey
- I'm Bailey. - Max.
Max Kenton.
他就是你的…… 是的
- So this is your... - Yeah, it's him.
Don't worry about it, OK?
我看你们……
I'm looking at you two and...
拜托你去把Noisy Boy放到店里。谢了
Just go and put Noisy in the shop, please? Thank you.
你和她呆在这儿，我先走
You're going to stay here with her while I'm on the road.
他给了你多少？ 你不该说这个
- How much did he give you? - You're coming at this the wrong way.
告诉我，我想知道
No, tell me. I want to know.
5千，好了吧
Fifty thousand, OK?
他给我5千把你签给她
He gave me $50,000 to sign you over to her.
可以闭嘴了吗？
Will you shut up now?
你把我卖了？
You sold me?
比这更糟
Sounds worse than it is.
是吗 我会好好照顾你的
- Really. - It's to take care of you.
分我一半，不用你照顾
Give me half the money and you won't have to.
你要去哪？ 给我钱，我会活得好好的
- Where are you going to go? - Give me the money. I'll be fine.
我跟你婶婶说好了夏天结束就把你送去纽约
I told your aunt I'll get you to New York at the end of the summer.
现在你关心起婶婶 Debra了？
Now you're concerned for Aunt Debra?
你5千块把我卖了，你欠我一半
You sold me for 50 grand. You owe me half!
我现在没钱，钱都花了去买机器人了，一分也没有了
I don't have it! I spent the money on a robot. It's gone! OK? Gone!
我要走了
I'm through here.
怎么样
What do we got?
Noisy Boy到了
Noisy Boy has arrived.
好多航空贴纸和标签
That's a lot of airline stickers and customs tags.
它都环游世界了 - London, Japan, Brazil, So Paulo... 伦敦，日本，巴西，圣保罗
- He's been all over the world.
两年没去北美了
Hasn't seen North American soil in over two years.
所以才那么实惠，天才
Maybe that's why you got such a good price, genius.
想说什么吗？
Decided to stay?
这是Bailey，这几周她会照顾你
This is Bailey. She'll be looking after you for a few weeks.
帮我照顾这个孩子几个星期
I need you to look after the kid for a few weeks.
我要一半钱 又要说这个？
- I want half that money. - Are we back to this again?
里面真的有个机器人拳击手？
Is there a real robot boxer in there?
Noisy Boy，听说过吗？
Noisy Boy's in there. You ever heard of him?
当然，他在2016年在WRB击败了 Rubicon
Of course. He fought Rubicon for the WRB belt in 2016.
我的娘，真是太棒了
Holy crap, he looks amazing.
她的复合装甲已经换过了，看看里面是否完好
His composite armor has been replaced. Let's see if the insides look as good.
我看他和 Rubicon打了20多次
I've watched that fight with Rubicon like 20 times.
他本来应该在第三轮撂倒他的
He should have had him in the third round,
但是Rubicon运气好然后结果了他
but Rubicon got lucky with a huge right and ended it.
别担心孩子，他站我们这边
Relax, kid, he's on our side.
不好笑 挺好笑的
- Not funny. - Kind of funny.
他可以识别声音，对吧？
You know he has voice recognition, right?
不可以 他没在过联盟
- No, he doesn't. - He didn't in the League.
Noisy在巴西的时候肯定被植入了程序
When Noisy fought in Brazil, they must have put it in.
巴西人对和机器人对话痴迷
Brazilians are crazy about that talk-to-your-robot crap.
向右，向左，上勾拳
Right, left, uppercut!
没用，向右，向左，上勾拳
Doesn't work. Right, left, uppercut!
我就是到便宜没好货，我们被坑了
I knew that price was too good to be true. We got screwed.
看看能不能修好它 他看上去真棒
- Let me see if I can fix it. - Look how good he looks, too.
给我两秒钟，我看看
Give me two seconds. Let me look at something!
为什么不看看他 别吵
- Why didn't you ask to look at it? - Relax!
日语？
Was that Japanese?
我看看能不能重设成英语
Let me see if I can reset him to English.
你怎么会日语
How do you know Japanese?
打游戏学的
Video games.
你打日本游戏？
You play video games in Japanese?
日本走私品一直都挺好
Japanese bootlegs are always better.
给我
Give me that.
重设成了，我还发现了这个命令矩阵
He's reset to English, and I found his command matrix.
他们下了一堆组合
They have pre-Ioaded a bunch of combinations.
应该列在这了
They should be listed here.
头槌
Top salvo!
我说过了吧
What did I tell you?
Gravity One Downtown!
风水轮流转啦
I was due for some good luck!
祝你好运 谢啦
- You're welcome. - Thank you.
Bailey帮我把它放到卡车里，我这就去把你的钱拿回来
Bailey, help me put him in the truck. I am going to go and get your money.
给我钥匙 我和你一起去
- Give me the keys. - I'm coming with you.
不要 为什么
- No, you're not. - Why not?
因为我不想带上你
Because I don't want you with me, OK?
要么我跟你去，要么你在下水道口钓钥匙
I'm either coming with you, or you're fishing for your keys in the sewer.
你自己决定，到底是哪个呢？老男人
Your choice. What's it going to be, old man?
哎呀，千钧一发啊
Oh, my God. That was close, wasn't it?
别那样！ 吓到你了，是吧
- Don't do that again. - That's scaring you, isn't it?
还要再来一次吗？
Don't do this again?
上车，上车。先给我钥匙
Get in. Just get in. Give me the keys first.
等我上车再说，谢了。
Wait till I get in the truck. Thanks, Big Pops.
真不错
Sweet ride.
系上安全带，然后闭嘴
Put on your seatbelt and don't talk.
所有赌注都我拿着
I'm taking all bets!
跟上，跟紧了
Keep up. Stay close.
Charlie Kenton到了
Charlie Kenton is in the house!
好吧，好吧 来吧
- All right, all right. - Come on, man!
是Noisy Boy？ 独一无二的
- Is that Noisy Boy? - The one and only.
是Noisy Boy哎！
That's Noisy Boy!
Noisy 在日本，Softer 机器人在那
Noisy's been in Japan. Softer bots over there.
你确定今晚要用它打？ 你有多少？
- Sure you want to fight him tonight? - What do you got?
你知道他会撂倒在场所有机器人的
He can take any bot in this place. You know it.
你随便挑
You can have any undercard you want.
5千押金
Five thousand guaranteed.
你的机器人赢一轮一千
A thousand every round your bot survives.
血战到底
Fight till the death!
不，我要直接进最后一场
No. Give me the main event.
别这样 他可是 Noisy Boy
- Come on. - This is Noisy Boy.
原装的Tak Mashido机器人
An original Tak Mashido bot.
他可是世界机器人联盟拳击手，怎么样
He was a World Robot League boxer. Come on!
你要战Midas，吗？
You want to fight Midas?
冠军得5万
Fifty thousand guaranteed, winner takes all.
5万？真的？5万，你说的
Fifty? Really, 50? Now you're talking.
听好了，听好了，不，看着我
Listen, listen. No, look.
听好了 等等
- Listen! - Give me a sec.
我们参加小比赛，拿了钱就走
We should take an undercard fight, make a little cash and get out of here!
首先，不是“我们”
First, there is no "we."
其次，他会打败Midas，我会赚好多钱
Second, he's going to crush Midas, and I'm going to make real cash!
我们就战Midas
We'll take Midas!
今晚，最后一场比赛
Tonight, our main event
嗜血杀手
features the gold-blooded killer!
这个扯皮的朋克机器人设计有感知疼痛的程序
This pimped-out punk
is programmed for pain!
上场的是强大的Midas
I give to you the mighty Midas!
以及他的对手
Against a bot
WRB的大家伙
who ran with the big boys in the WRB!
他曾经漂泊海外，现在回家了
He's been on an exile tour overseas, but now he's back home,
他准备好大干一场了
and he's ready to make some noise!
好好看看
Take your first look in a long time
at Noisy Boy!
碰撞殿堂
Crash Palace,
准备好来点破坏了吗？
who's ready for some destruction?!
赚钱吧！上吧
Let's make some money! Come on!
Midas对抗 Noisy Boy
We have Midas against Noisy Boy.
Noisy Boy 对决Midas
Noisy Boy against Midas.
等着一对已经等了一个晚上了，碰撞吧！
You've been waiting all night for this matchup, Crash Palace!
右勾拳
Scimitar right!
看到没
Did you see that?
一整晚好赚钱，赚大钱
Easy money, easy money all night. All night long!
加油，还没结束，上啊
Come on! It's not over yet. Let's go!
头槌！大炮
Skull salvo! Firefight!
好样的Noisy 还小比赛吗？
- Yeah! Go, Noisy! - Undercard, huh?
电击拳
Shockfist!
打那Shogun Trinity
Get in there. Shogun Trinity!
了结了他！重力撞击
Let's finish him. Gravity Slam, Uptown!
这狗娘养的疯了
This son-of-a-bitch is crazy!
Full Metal Feud干他
Full Metal Feud! Bring it!
Southpaw! Pain Revolution!
给你点颜色看看
I got something for you.
别想跑，你跑不了的
Don't you run from me! You can't run from me!
起来
Get up!
那违规了
That's illegal!
在地下格斗场没有规则
This is the underworld. There are no rules!
Midas 进攻了
Now we're seeing the Midas touch.
不，抬起手
No. Hands up!
滚回你的角落，婊子，男人点干死他
Get back in that corner, bitch, and take this whooping like a man!
他要被揍扁了
He's getting killed in there!
是语言操控，你指挥他做什么
It's a headset! You talk into it and you tell him what to do!
Panic Shield!
就是这个One-Two Overlord
That's it. One-Two Overlord!
不对不对 Shatter Punch
No, no. Shatter Punch!
碎他蛋
- Five Recall! - Get some!
猛击，猛击！
Jab, jab!
Right roundhouse!
他刚是吐Midas口水吗？
Did he just spit his juice in Midas's face?
你不能向Midas吐口水
No, you did not spit in Midas's face!
这是在碰撞宫殿，是疯狂的时候
It's party time now, Crash Palace!
用左手
Use your left!
Noisy想用左手反抗
Noisy's trying to do something with his one arm!
但是Midas见缝插针，游戏要结束了
But Midas pins him, and Daddy goes to work!
不不，起来啊
No, no! Get up!
行动啊
Get some!
动啊，离开角落
Move! Get out of the corner!
Midas! Midas! Midas!
卡普奇诺来了
Somebody's ready to serve up a decappuccino!
给你点颜色看看，准备好了吗
I got something for you! You ready?
晚安！Midas凯旋而归
Good night! That's a home run for Midas.
Noisy Boy屁滚尿流
And so long to Noisy Boy.
真糟糕，你饿不？
That sucked. You hungry?
我留下了 Noisy的声音识别板
I saved what's left of Noisy's voice recognition board.
除了那玩意儿他就一垃圾，我要从新搞个机器人了
Other than that, he's trash. I got to get a new robot together.
我的找到主机，怎么了？
I need to find a mainframe. What?
我讨厌汉堡 哪个小孩会讨厌汉堡
- I hate hamburgers. - What kid hates burgers?
好吧，不吃给我，你喝这个
Fine. More for me. Here, drink this.
你不该参加那场比赛的
You never should have taken that fight.
是吗是吗？谢了，天才
Really? Really? Thanks, genius.
你做事前有动脑子想过吗？
Do you even think about the stuff you do before you do it?
你根本不知道怎么打
You had no idea how to fight that fight.
这些组合口令你一半都不知道
Those combination codes, you didn't know what half of them even meant.
你自大的，毫无计划的就把他们丢那
You threw them in there cocky and half-assed.
连个机会也不给他 他没那么好
- You never gave him a chance. - He wasn't that good.
Noisy Boy是台很棒的机器人
Noisy Boy was a great robot.
以前，在联盟的时候很棒
Was. Was a great robot back in the League, back in the day.
但这里，在这里曾经很棒的机器人都报废了
But look around you. This place is where once great robots go to die.
所以就把它扔了？
So throw him away.
你就是这么做的事？不需要就扔了？
That's what you do, right? Anything you don't need you throw away.
Wow.
漫长的一夜
It's been a long night.
你想在屋子里睡觉就闭嘴上车
If you want to sleep indoors tonight, shut up and get in the truck.
别那样看着我，上车
Don't look at me like that way. Get in the truck!
他们给我400买头
They gave me 400 for his head.
你呆这儿，我去找找看
You stay put. I'm going to look for parts.
我跟你一起去，那饮料难喝死了
I'm coming with you. That drink has my heart pounding.
让我自己呆在车里脑子会炸的
If I sit in this truck by myself, my head will explode.
随便了，自己跟上
Whatever. Just keep up.
靠
Crap.
靠后
Stay back.
好了，走
All right, keep up.
探照灯是自动的，要把握好时机
These searchlights are automated, but you got to time them right,
跟紧了
so stay close.
好了
It's all right.
快点，快点
Come on, come on.
会被抓的 快点
- We're going to get caught. - Come on.
别担心，别担心
Easy, easy. Easy, easy.
快点，从这儿下去，走
Quick, quick. Down in here! Go, go, go!
机器人在东边，我们要很快去那
Robots are on the east side. We got to be quick in here.
过了这儿就没有探照灯了，快，走
Once we're through here, there's no more searchlights. Quick! Go!
到了 我们在找什么
- Here it is. - What are we looking for?
找一切可以把机器人组装起的东西
Anything I could use to put a fighting bot together.
看 怎么了
- Hey, look. - What?
好小哦
It's so small.
你出生前就有的了
Yeah. That's before your time.
第一代，最早的战斗机器人
That's a Generation One, the very first fighting bot.
他们想把它做得更像人，越像越好
They wanted them to look like us. The more human, the better.
时过境迁，把那放车里
Crazy how quick everything changed. Put that in the cart.
什么变了 好问题，人类拳击
- What changed? - A good question. Human boxing.
慢慢就没了 为什么
- It just faded. - Why?
因为钱，人们想看更多大屠杀，更多表演
Because the money moved on. People wanted more carnage, more show.
巴西地下格斗场有Gracies和Machados
You had the whole Brazilian underground, the Gracies, the Machados,
jiu-jitsu， Muay Thai和上千种款式
jiu-jitsu, Muay Thai, and a thousand styles in between.
各种各样，到处都是
Full-on ground-and-pound.
这个 这是什么
- Look at this. - What's that?
不知道
I don't know.
不错，好发现
Not bad. Good spot.
还是有像人的拳击手，有人的身体
You still had human fighters, human bodies,
你永远满足不了人类
so you couldn't give the people what they really wanted:
无拘无束的暴力
True, no-holds-barred violence.
下一步就是
The next logical step,
让人类原来那个舞台，让机器自相残杀
get the humans out of there and let the machines kill each other.
你怀念吗？
Do you miss it?
拳击，你怀念吗？ 小心
- Boxing. Do you miss it? - Careful.
什么？我想知道
What? I want to know.
小心，你在悬崖边
Careful, you're on a cliff.
很高呢 要是掉下去了，肯定会
That's a long way down. If you fell, you'd definitely...
Charlie救我
Charlie, help me!
Charlie!
- Charlie! - Max! Max!
Max!
别动 我好像在机器人手臂上
- Try not to move! - I'm on some sort of robot arm.
等等，别怕，把手给我，好的
Wait! Just easy, easy. Give me your hand. Nice and easy.
慢慢的，好样的，别往下看，看着我
Very slowly. Good. Don't look down. Look at me. Look at me.
好了，我抓到你了，别怕，我抓到你了
That's it! I've got you! You don't have to be scared. I got you!
太远了 没事的，我抓到你了
- It's so far! - It's OK. I got you.
慢慢的把手给我，好的
Give me your other hand. Nice and slow.
把另一只手也给我，慢慢的吗，碰到了，加油没抓到了
Just give me your other hand very slowly. Reach back. Come on. Reach!
看着我，我们一起
Look at me. We're going to do this together.
你和我，你只要看着我就好
You and me. Just look at me. That's it.
1 2 3
One... two... three!
好了，我抓到你了，抓到了，抓到了
That's it. I got you! I got you. I got you. I got you.
安全了，没事了
You're safe. You're safe.
好了，抓住你了
All right, I got you.
还好吧 恩
- You all right? - Yeah.
过来，放松
Come here. Easy. Easy.
没事吧
You all right?
没事吧 - Yeah.没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
我说过很危险的
I told you it was dangerous.
小心点，我们还在悬崖边
Careful. We're still on the edge here.
Charlie，这里有一整个机器人
Charlie, I think there's a whole robot in there.
那又怎么样，走啦
So what? Let's go. Come on.
我要把他带走，他救了我
I'm taking him with me. He saved my life.
他没救你，是我救了你，走啦
He did not save your life. I saved your life. Let's go.
把车推到悬崖边，我用绞车把他拉出去
Just bring the cart to the edge. I'll use the winch to get him out.
你要捡垃圾？要捡自己捡，我要走了
You want that piece of junk? You get the cart yourself. I'm through here.
这就是Noisy Boy剩下的？
This is what's left of Noisy Boy?
就这些
That's it.
他的头给碰撞宫殿门口做了很好的装饰
His head does make a nice addition to the front of the Crash Palace.
这不好笑 我们做个机器人，你和我
- It's not funny. - Let's get a robot, you and me.
好想法，你毁了一切
Good idea. You're broke. I'm almost there myself.
你失去了最好的机会 我们会再做一个
- You destroyed the best shot you had. - We'll put one together.
你很擅长这个，东西都在这儿了
You're brilliant at this. There's good stuff here.
这儿什么也没有 这里啊，看
- There's nothing here. - There is. Look.
这些废物，都是废物
All your junk is... it's junk.
你早就出局了
You're not even in the game anymore.
都是垃圾 我听见了，都是垃圾
- It's all garbage. - I heard you. It's garbage.
别跟我吼
Don't get loud with me.
是你自己的问题 什么意思
- You're your problem. - What's that supposed to mean?
我在这儿陪你带了够长的时间了
I have been here for you a long time.
比赛的时候，不比赛的时候，我厌倦了
In the ring, out of the ring, and the whole ugly spiral down, and I'm tired.
我父亲为你的事业投资了一切，我们爱……
My father invested everything he had in your fight career. We loved...
他乡家人一样爱你，这是他的家
He loved you like family. And this is his home.
我只是维持不让这里倒下，我就是我的计划
I'm just trying not to let it die. That's my plan.
你的计划是什么？
What's yours?
什么都玩完儿了，是么？
You're done, right?
结束了么？因为我想结束了，Charlie
You're finally done? Because I sure as hell am, Charlie.
我一无所有
I got nothing left.
好吧
All right.
也许那边那个
Maybe there's something here.
那孩子昨晚拉来的机器人，能帮我看看吗？
This robot the kid brought in last night. Would you look at it for me?
拜托
Please?
我从没见过这种东西，他是二代，但是很罕见
I've never seen anything like it before. He's Generation Two, but barely.
我找到了适合他的电池，帮他配上了老式的G2远程控制
I found a power cell that fits him, and I hooked him up to this old G-2 remote.
他可以动，但几乎是垃圾
You can move him around, but he's crap.
也许我可以给他找些保护条，赚点钱
Maybe I can get a sparring gig for him, make a few hundred bucks.
停
Stop.
是我的机器人
It's my robot!
我花了半晚上把他拖出来，它是我的
It took me half the night dragging him out of there. He's mine.
是你的？但是他身体里面的零件是我的
He's yours? Yeah. But the parts we're putting in him are mine!
你们两个白痴为他打架前看看他能不能启动
You idiots should see if he powers up before you fight over him.
你怎么了？
What happened to you?
当心，退后
Watch out. Stay back.
她有模仿功能，真少见
Looks like he's got a shadow function. That's pretty rare.
他可以模拟行动然后储存记忆
He can mime your movements and store them in memory.
能用的多吗 不多
- Is there anything here we could use? - Not much.
有个桶
There's a bucket...
有个我洗车的桶
There's a bucket I use to wash the truck.
打扫下，一股垃圾味
Use it and clean him up. He smells like crap.
也洗洗你自己，和他呆一起你也臭了
Wash yourself off, too, while you're at it. You stink.
我把它调成远程控制，很简单的
I switched him to remote. It's pretty basic.
用触发器控制他，让他走
Just use the toggles here to steer him and walk him.
你玩游戏吧？ 是的
- You play video games, right? - Of course.
一样的，这就是个1000磅机器人
Same idea, only this one's a thousand-pound robot.
太棒了
Cool.
原子
"Atom."
他叫Atom，可以让他打架吗
His name is Atom. Can we get him a fight?
我想他不是个拳击机器人
I don't think he was ever a boxing robot.
是G2型号，2014年产的 他是拳击机器人
He's a G-2, built in early 2014. He was a sparring bot.
肯定制造过这样的机器人
They must have built robots like this one
可以模仿其他机器人的战斗模式
that could mirror the fighting style of any other robot.
那可以让他打一场吗
OK, so can we get him a fight?
你没在听吗？他是拳击机器人
Are you not listening? He's a sparring bot.
可能会出击，但是不会有什么大的破坏力
Built to take a lot of hits, but never dishing out any real punishment.
你可以把它拆了卖了
You could always sell him off for parts.
可以让他打一场吗？ 可以让他打一场吗？
- Can't you get him a fight? - "Why can't you get him a fight?"
不到黄河心不死，是吧
God, you don't quit, do you?
你想让他参加拳击比赛被打散架吗？
You want me to put him in some bottom-rung scrap-fest to the death?
我看出来你在碰撞宫殿的时候下坏了
I saw how scared you were at Crash Palace.
你用这个机器人打一定会吓得尿裤子的
The places that would let you fight this robot would make you pee your pants.
好啊，让他打一场
Excellent. Get him a fight.
顽固的死小孩
Stubborn kid.
惊喜，惊喜
Surprise, surprise.
走走吧
Let's take a walk.
你听得懂我吗？
Can you understand me?
别担心，你的秘密我不会说出去的
Don't worry. Your secret's safe with me.
你认识Charlie很久了
You've known Charlie a long time.
太久了，我们都在这个体育馆长大
Too long. We both kind of grew up in this gym.
我父亲训练他的
My dad, he trained him.
那是他们，那个是Charlie
That's them. That's Charlie.
他喜欢当拳击手吗？
- What was he like? - As a boxer?
他什么都喜欢当 他很厉害
- As anything. - He was something.
他瘦，但是强壮
He was lean, tough.
无所畏惧，决不放弃
No quit, no fear.
来给你看点东西
Come here. I want to show you something.
我有2007年 Phoenix的这篇文章
I have this newspaper article from Phoenix 2007
Charlie战最强竞争者Nico Tandy
when Charlie fought Nico Tandy, the top contender.
你看了Nico Tandy的比赛？
You were at the Nico Tandy fight?
是啊，本来应该是Charlie的热身赛，应该赢得很轻松
I was. Charlie was supposed to be a warm-up fight, an easy win.
打败Nico根本不费吹灰之力
Nico wasn't even supposed to break a sweat, but...
但没人跟 Charlie说过，他一直逼近他
...nobody told Charlie that, so he just kept coming and coming at him.
看这个
Check this out.
那是 Charlie
That's Charlie.
一开始Nico不相信这个无名小卒那么厉害
First, Nico couldn't believe the balls on this nobody.
但 Charlie一直在逼近， Nico就害怕了
But Charlie kept coming, and that's when Nico looked scared.
真的？ 真的
- Really? - Really.
他完全在耍 Nico
He was toying with Nico.
最强挑战者，世界第二
The top contender, number two in the world,
Charlie再和他跳舞
and Charlie was dancing with him.
Charlie那晚厉害得不得了
Charlie was floating inches off the canvas that night.
像又幽灵一样，Nico根本看不清他
He was like a ghost. Nico couldn't even see him.
但我看得清
I could.
他的姿势太美了
He was beautiful.
太美了
然后呢？Charlie打败 Nico Tandy了吗？
So what happened? Did Charlie beat Nico Tandy?
不在第十二局的时候被Nico Tandy打中了，两次
No, Nico Tandy put me on my ass in the 12th round. Twice.
两次，然后灯就亮了
Second time for good. Lights out.
你得分高
You were ahead on the scorecards
地第2局的时候 Nico Tandy赢了
- going into the 12th round. - Nico Tandy rung my bell
然后连续三年蝉联不败冠军
and went on to be the undefeated world champ for the next three years.
他打败你了？ 是啊，打败了好多人
- He knocked you out? - Yeah. So did a lot of guys.
你也打败了好多人
You knocked a lot of guys out, too.
24和19，不算什么 但每次都赢
- 24 and 19. It's not exactly a career. - But every fight a knockout.
是啊 输或赢，
- Yeah. - Win or lose, fight's not over
直到把人打趴下比赛才结束
- till someone's on the mat. - Till someone's on the mat.
你爸教的 该死，他居然教你这个
- Your old man taught me that. - Damn straight he taught you that.
你还跟谁打过 收拾东西去
- Who else did you fight? - Go get your stuff together.
不需要 为了冠军而战吗？
I don't need to. Did you fight for the title?
是的，一个小时后出发
Yeah, you do. We leave in an hour. Go.
Wow. Here.
加油
Keep it.
谢了 不客气
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
我喜欢这孩子
I like that kid.
他也喜欢你
He likes you.
昨天我说的话 什么也别说了
- What I said yesterday was... - No, nothing more to say.
我今晚去Atlanta
I'm heading off to Atlanta tonight
看看能不能找到合伙人筹钱买个新机器人
to see if I can get a partner or raise money to get a new bot.
这就是你想要的对吧，我走就是了
That's what you wanted, right? Me gone?
是的，这就是我想要的
Yeah, that's what I wanted.
OK.
看
Look.
冠军在这，Zeus在这
The champ is here. Zeus is here.
是的
Yeah.
Zeus！这怪物两局之内战无不胜，两局
Zeus! No one has ever gone two rounds with this monster. Two rounds!
他是今晚的世界钢铁拳王
The champ puts his Real Steel world championship belt on the line tonight.
他胜券在握
He just may have a real fight on his hands.
Zeus最伟大的拳击机器人，没有之一。比赛结束，各位晚安
Zeus, greatest robot boxer of all time. Ever. End of story. Good night!
太棒了，棒极了 什么
- So cool. It's so cool. - What?
来
Come on.
听好了，我去找Finn
Listen up. I got to go find Finn.
你呆在这儿
I want you to stay in this area.
让开，冠军要过去Zeus 要过去
Out of the way. Champ coming through. Zeus coming through.
让开让开，冠军来了
Move, move. Champ coming through.
Farra Lemkova，Zeus父亲/女儿团队的幕后女儿
Farra Lemkova, daughter behind the father/daughter Zeus team.
传言说你父亲为Zeus出钱，但你才是真正的军师
They say your father's the money and you are the mind behind Zeus.
您真客气
You're very kind,
但真正的军师是 Tak Mashido
but I assure you, the mind behind Zeus belongs to the great Tak Mashido.
是什么吸引了这位天才，前任男孩奇迹
What did it take to lure the reclusive genius, former boy wonder
也是最受争论的最重要的机器人设计师
and arguably the most important bot designer in the history of the sport
是什么让他重出江湖
out of retirement?
干嘛不问他本人呢
Why don't you ask him yourself?
这是 Tak Mashido最伟大的作品吗？
Is this Tak Mashido's greatest creation?
Zeus在战斗中完全自主，他也一直在进化
Zeus is autonomous and constantly evolving during a fight.
带着适应力很强的系统
With his adaptive operating system,
他识别机型然后立即写出战斗编码
he recognizes patterns and rewrites his fight code instantaneously.
那您是说Zeus?
For myself and Joe Sixpack out there, are you saying that Zeus?
我说，不论遇到什么情况
I'm saying that no matter what happens in that ring...
比赛的结局永远不会改变
...the result of any fight is inevitable.
Zeus人挡杀人，佛挡杀佛
What Zeus sees...
...he kills.
厉害
Sweet.
我不会和你合作的
I'm never going into business with you.
我要休息下
I just need a break here.
把那个老式机器垃圾带出去，你老带些垃圾来
You got that old bot truck out there. You always got something in there.
我有个老式拳击机器人，分文不值
I got an old sparring bot, ain't worth the paint left on it.
我该怎么办？
What am I supposed to do with that?
去动物园，带他去动物园。 他们明天在这儿打
The Zoo. Take him to the Zoo. They fight there tomorrow.
我不会死在动物园的
Even I wouldn't be caught dead at the Zoo.
我只是需要贷款
I just need a little loan.
什么？
What?
你在开玩笑吧， Charlie 贷款
- You're serious, Charlie? - A loan.
几百块，你有多少给多少就行
Couple hundred. Few hundred. Whatever you got.
你知道我人好
You know I'm good for it.
我了解你，我也很喜欢你，伙计
I know you, and as much as I like you, dude...
你是个很糟糕的赌注，兄弟
...you're a bad bet, brother.
对，是啊
Right, yeah.
看到没，那是Axelrod的残骸
Did you see that? That's what's left of Axelrod.
你去哪儿了，我告诉过你不要乱跑
Where you been? I told you to stay put.
你没看见Zeus太帅了
You should have seen him. Zeus was, like, amazing!
帅，是么？ 简直不可思议
- Amazing, huh? - Unbelievable, yeah.
他把Axelrod一顿乱揍，太快了，不可思议啊
He was just peppering Axelrod with punches, but so fast. It was incredible.
Axelrod一拳也没打到他，连第一局也没撑过
Axelrod didn't even land a punch. He didn't even survive the first round.
你认为拳击就是那样？
Is that what you think boxing is?
Zeus打败了些破铜烂铁
Zeus beating up some piece of steel that they feed him?
Axelrod不是破铜烂铁，他是拳击机器人
Axelrod's not just some piece of steel. And that is what boxing is now.
太棒了，我爱死他了，我乐在其中
Deal with it. And I love it, and I'm in it now.
你乐在其中？你和你的G2机器人
You're in it now, are you? You and your G-2 sparring bot?
G2比那个更厉害，如果你让我们比赛你就会知道的
He's more than that. If you'd get us a fight, you'd see.
你运气好了，有个美妙的地方叫动物园
You're in luck, kid. There's a lovely place called the Zoo.
明天下午，你可以战一场
Tomorrow afternoon, you'll get your fight.
太好了 这也是最后一场
- Great. - And it will be the end.
我说过我讨厌汉堡
I told you I hate hamburgers!
是玉米煎饼
It's a burrito!
右上勾拳
Right uppercut.
左上勾拳
Left uppercut.
蹲下双手向上
Bend your knees. Rise up with both hands.
再来一次，蹲下双手向上
Again. Bend your knees. Rise up with both hands.
一晚没睡？
You been up all night?
是啊，我把它弄干净了
Yeah. I cleaned him up.
我用影子模式设计了战斗移动，然后同步到了远程里
I'm using shadow mode to program some fight moves and sync them to the remote.
恩，我看到了你示范的连续猛击
Yeah. I saw that double-up punch you were showing him.
那是致命的
That's lethal stuff.
来做这个
Let's do this.
先做早餐
Let's do breakfast first.
你知道你会带着破破烂烂的他回家对吗？
You know you're bringing him home in pieces, right?
走着瞧
We'll see.
交给我吧 我是Charlie Kenton这是 Max
- Let me deal with this. - Charlie Kenton. This is Max.
Kingpin叫我 Kingpin
Kingpin. Call me Kingpin.
好吧 Kingpin，这个…… 一局多少
- All right, Kingpin, so... - How much a round?
不是练习吗
We on a field trip?
好吧，他和我的 Metro打
All right. He can fight my robot Metro.
一百一局，两分钟
I'll give you a hundred bucks for one two-minute round.
成交吧 三百
- Take it. - Three hundred.
一百，宝贝儿，给你一百让你和 Metro打
One hundred. Baby boy, I'm going to give you $100 just to get in with Metro.
五百两局怎么样
How about 500 for two rounds?
两局？他一局都熬不过
Two rounds. Son, he ain't going to survive one round.
要是熬过了呢 不可能
- What if he does? - He ain't.
要是他行呢！
Let's just say he does.
要是一局没倒下
If he's still standing after one round...
给你一千块
...I'll give you a thousand bucks.
闭嘴
Shut it!
要是他挂了，少年
But if he dies in there, which he will, junior...
我要他的尸体
...I get to keep what's left.
选一百的
Take the hundred.
成交
Deal.
来吧，我们上
We're on. We on!
走吧
Let's go!
你应该选一百的 我会赚一千
- You should have taken the hundred. - I got us a thousand.
是啊，除非他赢了
Yeah, if he wins.
要我操作吗
You want me to drive?
是我的机器人，我来
He's my bot. I got this!
这不是打游戏，是来真的
This ain't a video game. This is for real. Right here.
你说他会变成破烂，要是没有呢
You said he's coming home in pieces. What difference does it make?
好吧
All right.
我要上了
I got this.
要上了，要上了
Let's get it on! Let's get it on!
像香港乒乓球队那样上吧
Let's get it on like Ping-Pong in Hong Kong!
给个铃，给个铃
Give me a bell! Give me a bell!
别看 Atom看你的对手
Don't watch Atom. Watch your opponent.
看脚，他踩你了
Watch out for that foot. He's looking to pin you.
我说了让你看脚的
I told you to watch for that foot plant. Come on.
他的大锤来了
Here comes the sledgehammer.
看到没
Did you see that?
上啊，干掉他 别对他叫，控制他
- Come on! Get him! - Don't yell at him, control him.
向右，退后
Slip right. Back step.
躲开
Duck.
不客气 闭嘴，你什么忙也帮不上
- You're welcome. - Shut up! You're not helping!
我可帮了大忙
Actually, I think I am.
反手击，快点，别停
Backhand. You got speed on this guy. Just keep moving. Bob.
离开角落，别听，跳着迂回前进
Slip out of that corner. Keep moving! Bob and weave!
就这样，现在，听我指挥
That's it! Now you're listening to me.
它能承受这一击，你的机器人可以承受
He can take a hit. I'll give you this. Your bot can take a hit.
最好赶紧脱离，不然死的很难看
You better slip that headlock. This ain't gonna end well for you.
我正在
I'm trying!
30秒
Thirty seconds!
30……半分钟
Thirty... Half a minute.
半分钟，动起来，别停
Half a minute! Keep moving! Just move!
你有20秒
You've got 20 seconds!
一千块呢，20秒，结果了他
That's a thousand bucks. Twenty seconds. Let me take over!
动啊 动啊
Move, then. Move!
块
Come on.
起来Atom，起来Atom
Get up, Atom. Get up, Atom.
一起倒数，一起倒数
Count with me! Count with me! One!
起来 你在和机器说话？
- Get up! - You know you're talking to a machine?
Four! Five! Six!
起来Atom
Get up, Atom!
冲啊冲啊
All the way up! All the way up!
好样的 好样的
Yes! Yes!
我要修理他
I'm going to fix it!
I'm going to fix it! Come on, now.
这一千块 是的一千
- This thousand bucks... - Yeah, thousand.
双倍还是什么也不要 他来不了另外一局了
...double or nothing he can't make another round.
谢了 成交，双倍还是一无所有
- Yeah, thanks anyway. - Deal. Double or nothing.
男孩成交，继续战斗
Baby boy said it! We're back on! We on!
疯了吗？你刚丢了一千
Are you crazy? You threw away a thousand bucks!
他都站不稳了
He can barely stand up in there.
我真的很需要钱
Look. I really need the money.
我知道，会成功的
I know. Let's work.
天啊
Jesus.
看，看 我成功了
- Watch that. Watch that. - I got that.
成功了 系统失败了
- I got it. - That's a system failure!
失败了 他倒下了
- I don't got it. - He's going down.
好 不
- Yes! - No!
倒数
Start the count!
倒数啊
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five! Six! Seven!
Eight! Nine!
Ten!
你做到了，我们成功了
You did it! We did it! Wow!
走吧 带上你的机器人
Time to go. Come on. Grab your robot.
我知道！我知道！
I know, I know! I know! I know!
Kingpin付钱
Kingpin, pay up.
耶，耶，耶，我知道了，我知道了
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I know, I know, I know.
-我们赢了！-我们走。赶紧，赶紧
- We owned! - Let's go. Come on, come on.
-有空么？-我这里有场比赛给你。
- Yeah? - Have I got a fight for you.
周六晚上，四千英镑保底。赢了七千。
Saturday night. Guaranteed four grand. Seven if he wins.
四千？好。我们走
Four grand? You're on. Let's go!
Bailey，那是我的。他赢的。
Bailey, it's me. He won.
你能相信么？那孩子的机器人赢了。
Can you believe that? The kid's robot actually won.
我知道。
I know.
高兴么？我的天啊。耶
Happy? Oh, my God. Yeah.
He's been bit. He's been bit real bad.
无论如何。。。
Anyway...
我只想让你知道。
I just wanted you to know.
猛击，猛击。上勾拳
Jab, jab, hook.
我认为你最好注意下脚步
I think you have to move your feet.
你的脚，脚
Your feet. Feet.
很好，孩子
Nice moves, kid.
你在外面多久了？
How long you been out here?
来看看
Check it out.
我花了一晚上时间弄的
I just spent the night doing something I think is amazing.
太惊奇了。如果可以的话，你懂的？
Incredibly amazing. If it works, you know?
你知道他的遥控器是坏的？-是的
- You know his remote was spotty? - Yeah.
我把他给拆了，我们再也不需要他了
I killed it. Got rid of it. We don't need it anymore.
你怎么？
How did you?
我不得不重新开始。
I had to start over.
但是我可以把Ambush的零件
But I was able to use the spin frame from Ambush
装在 Noisy Boy身上
and take the circuitry sleeve out of Noisy Boy,
而且成功了
and it works.
完全有效，绝对可以。
He knows nothing, but it works. It really, really works.
怎么样？
What works?
我打开它
I got to turn it on.
左勾拳，上勾拳
Left jab, right uppercut!
日本！
Japan!
你弄好了语音识别系统？
You put Noisy's voice recognition into Atom?
-太聪明了，孩子。-聪明？
- Pretty smart, kid. - Smart?
我TMD就是个天才！
It could be genius!
这绝对是人类历史上最不可思议的事情。
It could be the most incredible thing in the history of the entire world!
你把所有苏打水喝光了？
Easy there, chief. Did you drink all these sodas?
我可能还有点。我需要你教它打拳
I might have had a few. I need you to teach him to box.
你开玩笑吧？它是老式机器人不适合的
Are you kidding me? He's not advanced enough to handle Noisy's voice command.
所以他需要你教它
So he needs your moves. Your commands.
从零开始。忘了吧
- Start over from the ground up. - Forget it.
你是个拳击手。
You were a boxer.
昨天在动物园，你看到它行的
Yesterday at the Zoo, you could see things happen before they even happened.
我已经很久没打拳了，而且再也不会打了
I haven't boxed in a long time. I'm not starting now.
那谁教它呢？-你就可以了
- Who's going to teach him to fight? - You're doing fine.
你不需要我的，抱歉
You don't need me. Sorry.
这舞蹈太帅了！
That was really cool, though, that dance.
你可以在周六晚上跳
You should do that on Saturday night.
别嘲笑我。-我说真的
- Don't make fun of me. - I'm serious.
开打的铃声响起前，你可以表演下
Before the fight, when you guys take the ring, you should do it.
我绝不在一堆看拳击塞的观众面前和一个机器人跳
There's no way I'm dancing with a robot in front of a boxing crowd.
你开玩笑么？这是一场表演
Are you kidding me? This is just a show.
人们就是喜欢这些没见过的新鲜玩意
People want to see something they've never seen.
看。你可以看看所有牛B人物
Look. You think of all the greats.
拳王阿里, 甜心合唱团
Think Ali, Sugar Ray, Prince Rakim, Gammer,
他们都有他的别名
they all had their nicknames.
他们都有他们的私人特点
They had their personas. They all had flair.
你呢？你没有太多的机器人，但是你有一个会跳舞的机器人
Now you? You might not have much robot, but with that dance, you got flair.
加上你是个孩子，人们会喜欢你的
Plus, you're a kid. People love that kid thing.
你多大？9岁，10岁？我11了！
- What are you? Like nine? Ten? - I'm 11.
你确定你11了？
Are you sure you're 11?
当然。
Yes. I'm sure I'm 11.
好吧，重点是人们喜欢你那样
Anyway, the point is people want to see that.
你没骗我吧？
You're really not messing with me?
没有，人们肯定喜欢你的
I am not messing with you. They're going to love it.
好的。但是
- Cool. - But...
怎么了？你不帮我的话，我不会跳的
- What? - I won't do it unless you help me.
我不会跳舞，你自己就可以了
I can't dance. You're on your own there.
我是指拳击
No. Boxing.
好吧，我明白了。我给机器人设置程序
- Oh, I see. - I program the robot.
你教它拳击。你来跳舞
- You teach him to box. - And you dance.
你跳舞
And you dance.
好的。好的？
- Yeah. - Yeah?
成交。
Deal.
绝对酷毙了！
It's going to be cool.
牛B
Nice.
你将要面对大家伙。向上挥拳
You're going to be punching guys bigger. You're going to have to punch up.
对了
That's it.
很好
Nice.
你也是，老男人
You, too, old man?
赶紧，让我们开始正事吧
Come on. Let's get to work.
很好！再来一次
Nice! Let's do that again.
很好，三连击。
Nice. Three-punch combo.
继续
Combo.
再来。
Again. Again.
快点，快点，很好
Faster. Faster. Nice.
你都不用喘气的，我喜欢。
You're not even out of breath. I like it.
让我们看看你步伐如何
Let's see how you move.
很好
That's good.
向前一步。左勾拳！左勾拳
Step around! Left hook! Left hook!
对了。
That's it. Every time.
向上
Upper cut!
很好，伙计！
Great fight, fellas.
105.5, WRUT,机器人拳击厅
105.5, WRUT, the satellite home of robot boxing.
两位，你们给我带来了什么呢？
Caller two, what do you got for me?
你听说过那个小机器人么
Have you heard about this little bot out there, his name is Atom?
是的
Oh, yeah.
我跟我的伙伴那天晚上看到他在跳舞
My buddies and I saw him the other night, and he dances.
跳舞？是的
- Did you say "dances"? - You heard me.
他和那个小男孩有一场赛前表演
He dances pre-fight with this little kid,
观众们都为他俩发狂了
and the crowd went nuts for these two.
你先把那骗人的玩意放一边去
You put the gimmick aside for a second,
我刚拿到这个机器人打败过的名单
and I'm holding here a list of the bots he's beaten.
Chaos.Wall Street. One-Eyed Jack，这些被他干掉的机器人都挺强的么
Chaos. Wall Street. One-Eyed Jack. No slouches on that list, right?
这矮个机器人把他们全打败了
Atom's fought them all, beat them all.
这家伙速度很快，他避开了大家伙的攻击。
This bot is fast! He escapes shots from these bigger bots, it's insane!
毫无疑问。我来告诉你，听好了，记住这个名字
No doubt. I'm telling you, listeners, remember this name:
Atom.对，A-T-O-M.
Atom. That's right, A-T-O-M. This bot is one to watch.
可怕的攻击。谢谢，谢谢
- Awesome fight, sir. - Thanks, thanks.
打的很好。
Great fight.
打的太精彩了。谢谢
- You guys put on a good show. - Thanks.
我们像邀请你为我们打场比赛
We'd like to invite you to fight on our card,
周五晚上，底特律的赛场
Virgin America Spectrum Detroit, Friday night.
对了，就是WRB联赛
Right. That's a WRB... That's a League fight.
太牛B了，你觉得如何，准备好这场比赛了么？
Damn right it is. What do you say, fellas? You ready for the show?
见鬼
Heck, yeah.
虽然是邀请赛，但仍然是联盟赛呢
It's the undercard, but it's still a League fight.
我只需要你放松下，你要放松，别紧张
I just want you to be relaxed. I want you to be relaxed.
别怕，没有任何东西能难到我们
No freaking out. Don't get all freaky-deaky on me.
如果你怕了，所有的东西都会没了
You go freaky-deaky, this whole thing can go south.
不管你做什么，一定要高兴，高兴，明白么？
Whatever you do, have fun, have fun. You got to have fun, you understand me?
我们走这么远来这里就是为了克服一切困难
We've come too far to get out there and freak out and blow this whole thing.
我们就是来玩的，搞定一切
We're going to have fun, and we're going to not freak out!
我们就算是输了，我们也要去
We're going to stay loose, and we're just going to bam him.
我一生都在为了这里，我们要。。
I've spent my whole life waiting to get here. We're going to...
我跟你说过什么。当我说不要怕的时候相信我，明白么
I tell you what. Trust me when I say no freaking out. You got it?
了解。很好
- I got it. - Good.
你被邀请去见Lemkova Suite，请跟我来
You have been invited to Lemkova Suite. Follow me, please.
谁？再说一次
What was that? One more time.
Lemkova Suite. Zeus Suite.
当然，让我们去冠军的屋里。
Sure. Yeah. Let's head up to the champ's suite. Sure.
哇
Wow.
先生，我是Farra Lemkova。你好，我是Charlie Kenton,
- Gentlemen, I'm Farra Lemkova. - Yeah. I'm Charlie Kenton, and...
当然，这是Tak Mashido
And this, of course, is Tak Mashido.
太牛B了，它是Tak Mashido
Holy shit. It's Tak Mashido.
我知道你今天晚上有场重要的比赛，所以我特地过来。
I know you have a very important fight tonight, so I'll get right to it.
虽然我不好这口，但是我喜欢
It's a little far from the action for my liking. It's nice. I like it, though.
很好，哇。非常棒
Very nicely... Wow. That's a great shot.
看那个。想来个合影么？介意么？
Look at that. You want an autograph? Would you mind?
我想买下你的机器人
I'd like to buy your robot.
他可以做Zeus的陪练机器人。而且我会付钱的
He'd be useful sparring bot for Zeus. And for that I'm willing to pay.
$200,000.
成交。-他不是拿来卖的
- Done. - He's not for sale.
当然，它是，我们很确定。。-他不卖的
- Of course he is. We can definitely... - He's not for sale.
离比赛还有15分钟
You are 15 minutes away from getting in the ring with Twin Cities,
你们将要面对一个非常凶残的机器人
a vicious League bot.
所以，想清楚，一旦比赛铃声响起，你的机器人就成一堆废铁了
So, to be clear, my offer stands until the starting bell.
我们很清楚，不卖的
OK. And just to be clear, he's not for sale!
现在不卖，永远不卖
Not now, not ever.
给你一分钟时间考虑
Give me a minute to clear this up, OK?
Tak,怎么样？Max!
Tak, how are you? Max!
聪明点，我知道你爱他
Be smart. I know you love him,
但是20分钟后，可能什么也剩不下来了
but in 20 minutes there may be nothing left to love.
好好考虑下。接受这笔交易。你好好考虑下。
- Think about it. Take the offer. - You think about it.
他为什么要买？因为他和其他机器人不同
Why does she want Atom? Because he's different from other bots!
是的，他不同。他更小，更弱
Yeah, he's different. He's smaller, weaker,
而且他将被其他机器人干掉。-他是个拳击手
- and he's going to get his ass kicked. - He's a boxer.
我们教它打拳。是你教它打拳
We taught him to box. You taught him to box!
他值得的。我也这么认为
- That's worth something. - I think it is, too.
我认为他值得20万美元
I think it's worth 200 grand. Two hundred grand.
我们可以干很多事情
We can go round and round this all night long.
看着我
Look at me.
绝对不可能的
But it's not going to happen.
我有场比赛
I got a fight to get to.
女士们和先生们，今晚
Ladies and gentlemen, tonight,
欢迎来到底特律观看
the march towards the Real Steel Championship
锦标赛前的热身赛
makes its way through Detroit's
由美国Virgin集团赞助!
Virgin America Spectrum!
首先上场的是
Kicking off the evening, in our first undercard,
来自双子城的
the two-headed tyrant,
“双头暴君”
Twin Cities!
他的对手是头一次参加专业联赛的
Opposing Twin Cities, in his first professional fight,
无名小卒
hailing from parts unknown,
Atom!
很好，老板。谢谢
- Nice work, boss. - Thanks.
你把他调到战斗模式了么？是的
- Did you switch him to fight mode? - Of course.
这家伙很难对付。Atom 可以的
- This bot is tough to put down. - Atom can do it.
看按。你看到那些控制台傍边的人了么
Look over there. You see those geeks with the joysticks and consoles?
他们控制他们的机器人做各种动作
They're controlling everything their bot does.
他们监视他的整个系统
They're monitoring his systems,
注意观察
seeing what he sees, stadium feeds of the fights.
这可不像那些地下比赛
This is not like the underground handheld remote bots
我们要开打了，这可是联赛，站在那
we've been fighting. This is the League. Stand on that.
我们做什么呢
So what do we do?
我们要聪明点，耐心点，祈祷吧
We fight smart, we be patient. And pray.
认真祈祷吧
Seriously, pray.
准备！
Ready!
准备，举起手来
- Ready! - Hands up.
准备，打！
Fighters ready! Fight!
开始
Engage.
右边!后面。右边，左边，遮挡
Slip! Right! Lean back. Right, left! Cover up!
闪避，左边
Duck! Left roundhouse!
该死
Damn it.
左边，右边！遮挡
Lean left! Lean right! Cover up! Cover up!
你在那干嘛？他挨了太多下了
- What's going on in there? - He's taking too many hits.
举起手！
Get your hands up!
离开角落。快！
Get out of that corner! Move!
在那儿会被杀死的！ 告诉他该怎么做！
He's getting killed in there! Tell him what to do!
那家伙距离我们有两个头，一英尺的距离，没有盲点
That guy's got two heads, a foot of reach on us, and no blind spot.
他一定有弱点。找到它！
He's got to have a weakness. Find it!
等等，等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait.
右肩，右肩。 右肩！一定有问题！
Right shoulder, right shoulder, right shoulder! He's got a tell!
每次他右手扔炸弹的时候，他的肩膀有点不灵活！
He's got a hitch in his shoulder every time he throws that right bomb!
抓到他弱点了！ 你看？又来了一次！
We got him! See? Here it comes again!
低头躲闪！转身！ 向左侧移！全力挥臂！一，二！
Duck! Spin! Slide left! Roundhouse! One, two!
后退，后退 后退. 向右闪
Backstep. Backstep. Backstep. Lean right.
快，Charlie！就是那儿！
Come on, Charlie! Get in there!
必须靠近他不能够不到我们的地方！
Got to get in close where he can't use that size and reach on us!
身体左侧！身体右侧！ 身体左侧！
Left to the body! Right to the body! Left to the body!
好耶！有效！
Yeah, it's working!
呆在台阶下！左！右！左！
Stay downstairs! Left, right, left!
这些编程模式不好用 左边！右勾拳，闪开！
- These program modes aren't working. - Left! Right hook, slip!
右上勾拳！左上勾拳！ 向左蹲下！向右反击！
Right uppercut! Left uppercut! Duck left. Counter right!
打倒他，Atom! 下面让你尝尝查理的特殊技能
- Get him, Atom! - Here comes the Charlie Special.
三连击！ 出去！回来！反击！
Three-punch combo to the body! Out! In! Counter!
二-一-二！ 二-一-二！
- Two-one-two! - Two-one-two.
跟住他！向右刺！
Stay on him! Lunging right!
别让他躲开，直击身体！ 直击头部！
Don't let him go. Right to the body! Straight right to the head!
我们的系统崩溃了！
We got a systems crash!
干掉他，Atom!
Get him, Atom!
这不可能，天啊
This is not happening, man.
把他甩开，Charlie！ 向左转！
- Put him away, Charlie! - Spin left!
向右转！
Spin right!
干掉他！
Finish him!
快点！ 右手上勾拳！
- Do it! - Right uppercut!
他倒下了！
He's down!
一！二！三！
One! Two! Three!
四！五！六！
Four! Five! Six!
我们打赢他了，坚持下去！
We got him. Stay down!
他出局了！他出局了！
He's out! He's out!
好耶！
Yeah!
Corner! Corner!
Corner! Corner. Corner! Corner.
胜利了！
Victory!
在第一轮
In a time of one minute, 47 seconds
耗时1分47秒钟，
of the first round,
Atom打败了...
Atom has defeat...
感谢大家今晚的光临！
I want to thank everyone for coming out tonight!
我们来自垃圾厂的小机器人得到了一次联盟对决的机会
Our little bot from the junkyard got a shot at a League fight.
那怎么样？
How about that?
我只想对一个不愿提及姓名的特殊女孩说，
And the last thing I want to say to a special girl who won't be named,
Farra Lemkova. Farra Lemkova.
而不是买我的机器人，用你的钱来控制这项运动...
That instead of buying my robot, using your money to control this sport...
这就对了！ 我还没完
- That's it! - I'm not done.
为什么不给那个小家伙重重一击？
Why not give the littlest guy the biggest shot?
因为我保证如果你给他一击，他会让你大吃一惊！
Because I bet if you give him a shot, he'll surprise you!
难道你不想看看一个小家伙
Wouldn't you like to see a little guy
在钢拳冠军赛中得到一次对决机会么？
get a shot at the Real Steel Championship?
我将挑Zeus.
I challenge Zeus to a fight.
时间，地点，随便挑！
Any time, any place, anywhere!
你说了算！我们一定到！
You name it! We will be there!
我去安排一下这场比赛！
I'm going to get us that fight!
Atom, Atom, Atom... Atom, Atom, Atom...
你可真有种，敢那样挑战宙斯.
That was a ballsy move, you challenging Zeus like that.
就是应该那样的
That's one thing to call it.
很多人都希望看到那一幕
A lot of people would like to see that.
你他妈说的很对，他们会的 你听到那个孩子说的么？我的天！
- You're damn right they would. - You listening to this kid? Jeez!
打的好，伙计们 谢谢
- Good fight, fellas. - Thanks, man.
看看这个，我们来庆祝吧 好啊
- Look at this. Let's celebrate. - Yeah.
好了，三七开，对吧？ 对， 七成给我，三成给你
- All right, 70-30, right? - Yeah, 70 for me and 30 for you.
太对了 太有趣了
- That's so right. - That's very funny.
我告诉你我们不应该卖掉他 好吧，不，不，不
- I told you we shouldn't have sold him. - OK. No, no, no.
我现在记住了，谁是对的？ 说谁是对的？说"Max是对的"
I remember now. Who's right? Say who's right. Say "Max is right."
好吧，好吧，好吧
All right, all right. All right.
我们是一个好团队 不，不，Max是对的
- We're a good team. - No, no. Max is right.
不敢相信 谢谢，双子城
That was unbelievable. Thank you, Twin Cities.
我们定了？ 是啊
- We set? - Yeah.
开始吧 查理男孩
- Let's do it. - Charlie boy.
Ricky，我正要给你打电话 哦，好的
- Ricky, I was just going to call you. - Oh, yeah.
我真的正要给你打电话
I actually really was going to call you.
别担心那个了
Don't worry about that.
打的真他妈的漂亮
That was a heck of a fight.
恭喜你们两位 真不错
Congratulations to both of you. That was good.
打的很精彩 干的不错，年轻人
It was an amazing fight. That was a great job, young man.
来吧，伙计 什么？
- Come on, man. - What?
你当真的？ 你觉得我是在开玩笑
- You serious? - You thought I was joking
当我说我差一点就打败你的时候？
when I said I'd beat you within an inch of your life?
他觉得这是个玩笑 这不是玩笑
He thought that was a joke. It wasn't a joke.
我这儿有个孩子，我有你的钱 我们没有问题了吧
I got a kid here. And I have your money. We don't have a problem.
我确定你有
I'm sure you do,
但是我们知道这不仅仅是钱的问题吧，不是么？
but I think we know it's about much more than money, don't we?
好吧，你们想要什么？ 你们想要两万五，三万？你想要三万？
All right. What do you want? You want 25, 30? You want 30 grand?
我这儿有现金 是，好的
- I got the money in cash here. - Yeah, right.
快走！ Max，走！走啊！快跑！
Let's go! Max, go! Go, go! Run!
快跑！快，跟上，跟上！ 抓住他！
- Run! Come on. Keep up, keep up! - Get him now!
跑啊！快点！
Run! Come on!
放开他！放开他！
Get off him! Get off him!
过来！
Come here!
嘿， Ricky.
Hey, Ricky.
那是他的钱！ 别把他也牵扯进来！
That's his money! Leave him out of this!
住手！
Stop!
把钱都拿走，全都拿走吧
Take all his money. Take it all.
你朋友真是个大傻逼，孩子
Your friend's a real dirtbag, kid.
他是我爸爸！
He's my father!
好吧，看起来不只是差一点点吧
Well. Looks like a little less than an inch of your life.
好吧，伙计，那会教训他的
Well, buddy, that will teach him.
正像是以前的时光，查理男孩！
Just like old times, Charlie boy!
我们走，孩子们
Let's go, boys.
很抱歉，Max.我很抱歉，抱歉
I'm sorry, Max. I'm sorry. Sorry.
我们在这里干什么呢？ Max，只是...
- What are we doing here? - Max, just...
那是Farra么？她给你打电话了，不是么？ 我们要去参加Zeus挑战赛
Is it Farra? She called you, didn't she? We're going to get the Zeus fight.
它不是Zeus的人，我从来没想过会这样，而且...
It's not the Zeus people. I've been thinking about all this, and...
Max! Max!
见到你很高兴
It's so good to see you.
她在做什么？ 现在最好是你和她走
- What is she doing here? - It's better if you go with her now.
我们惨败，所以你叫她来接我？
We get beat up, so you call her to come and get me?
他被打败了.我告诉过你他不能照顾好自己的！
He's been beat up. I told you he couldn't take care of him!
是啊，我叫了她 看看我们，我们一团糟.
Yeah. I called her. Look at us. We're a mess.
我们没事，她可以走了！
We're fine. She can leave!
Atom打的很不错 我们会把钱赚回来的
Atom's fighting good. We can make the money back.
Charlie，求你了
Charlie, please.
只是...
Just...
Charlie，我们做的很好
Charlie, we're doing so good.
Charlie，求你了，别这样
Charlie, please, no.
不要，不要，不要这样
Don't. Don't. Don't.
求，求你了
Please. Please.
相信我，孩子 这样最好，好么？
Trust me, kid. It's better this way, all right?
我知道你可能觉得你知道什么是对的，但是你并不知道
I know you think you know what's right, but you don't.
你还太年轻，你不会懂的
You're too young. You don't know.
看着我，相信我
Look at me, trust me.
而且法律上，她有监护权 所以我还能做什么？
And legally she has custody, so what can I do?
我能做什么？
What can I do?
我不需要你的钱，Marvin
I don't want your money, Marvin.
Max，我们有自己的游泳池
Max, we have our own swimming pool
我们有一个大热水缸，还有很多可以玩的超有趣的玩具
and we have a hot tub and a lot of super fun toys to play with.
你不想和他们一起玩么？ 很有趣的
Do you want to play with them? It's going to be fun.
这发生了什么？
What's going on?
他不想和我说话 所以多亏了你，Charlie.
He won't even talk to me, so thanks for that, Charlie.
我去车上等
I'm going to wait in the car.
你不想谈谈，没关系，我来说
You don't want to talk, fine. I'll talk.
你想让我说什么？说我很抱歉？
What do you want me to say? I'm sorry?
你知道从第一天起就是这样
You knew from day one what this was.
是你决定开始这段旅程的
You decided to take the ride.
你认为我，你，和从垃圾场捡到的小机器人
You thought me, you, and a little robot from the junk heap
能够飞黄腾达？
were going to ride off into the sunset?
不，你忘记了我是谁！
No, you forgot who I was!
你应该得到更好的...
You deserve better...
...比我更好的
...than me.
求你说点什么吧？
Will you say something, please?
我试过了，你想从我这里得到什么？
I tried. What do you want from me?
我想求你为我而战
I want you to fight for me.
我想要的就只有这样
That's all I ever wanted.
别问了
Don't ask.
就是说不行，Max
So no Max.
最好这样 Marv和Debra有钱，Max准备好了
It's better this way. Marv and Debra have money. Max is set.
你没有注意到他看你的方式？
Did you not see the way he looked at you?
就是我看我父亲的那种方式
That's the way I looked at my dad.
即使到现在我愿意放弃一切挽回曾经的那些
Even now I would give anything to have that back.
你爸爸很特别 他从第一天起就默默的在角落里守护你
Your dad was special. He was in your corner from day one.
我，来吧，我搞砸了
Me, come on. I blew it.
我搞砸了
I blew it.
当Max出生时，我...
When Max was born I just...
...吓坏了
...freaked out.
但是有些事情总比什么都没有的要好
But something would have been better than nothing.
我不知道从哪里开始
I wouldn't know where to start.
是的，你知道 我不知道
- Yeah, you do. - I don't.
你知道 不
- You do. - No.
你知道
You do.
我要走了
I got to go.
两百英里就为了一吻
Twelve hundred miles for a kiss.
值得的，值得的
Worth it. Worth it.
去追上他，Charlie.
Go get him, Charlie.
你说话的方式像我爸爸
You sound like your dad.
听着，我知道你认为我已经放弃了你，
Look, I know you think I abandoned you,
我猜我原本也是这么打算的
and I guess I did originally.
然后你出卖了我
Then you sold me.
Charlie. Charlie.
在这儿你已经没有什么事了
You have no business being here.
那是真的 你已经得到了全部抚养权，他是你的了
That's true. You've got full custody. He's yours.
我知道我对这个孩子做了太多的错事，但是请允许我...
And I know I've done all kinds of wrong by this kid, but if you'll let me...
...做一件正确的事情
...I'd just like to do one thing right.
好吧
Right.
我们在哪儿？ 你出卖了我
- Where were we? - You sold me.
是的，对，就是发生了
Right, yeah, that happened.
等等，什么？ 我们已经破产了
- Wait, what? - Then we had our asses kicked.
你就睡在卡车架子上，太糟糕了
And you slept on a shelf in a truck, and it was awful.
而且危险 相当危险
- And dangerous. - Really dangerous.
我是说，我知道，天啊，我很抱歉
I mean, I know. God. I'm sorry.
你来就是为了这个？ 来说对不起？
That's why you came? To say you're sorry?
不，我是说，是的，是的
No. I mean, yes. Yes.
但是不，不，我来告诉你我听到的关于你的事
But no. No, I came to tell you that I heard you.
我懂了 我有点迟钝，但是我懂了
I got it. I'm a little slow, but I got it.
我知道你已经流浪了，但是我没有陪你，我原本可以的
I know you had a bum ride, and I wasn't there and I should have been.
我原本可以的
I should have been.
你妈妈...
Your mom was...
你妈妈很酷，不是么？
She was cool, wasn't she?
她是的
She was.
她是最酷的
She was the coolest.
是的，没错
Yeah, she was.
对于发生在她身上的事我很抱歉
And I'm sorry about... what happened with her.
而且我不能挽回那些日子了， Max,
And I can't get those years back, Max,
但是现在我在这里...
but I'm here right now...
...如果你准备好的话，我要准备战斗了
...and if you're up for it, I'm ready to fight.
我们要挑战Zeus
We got the Zeus fight.
什么？
What?
不，不，我们不能
No, no, we didn't.
你得到了Zeus挑战赛
You got the Zeus fight.
你觉得怎么样，Debra?
So what do you say, Debra?
我们能做最后一件事情么？
Can we do this one last thing?
就一晚上 我们只需要一晚上，谢谢
- One night. - It's all we need. Thank you.
我们可能会惨败，但是至少我们虽败犹荣
We'll probably get our asses kicked, but at least we'll go down swinging.
是么？你觉得怎么样？
Yeah? What do you say?
欢迎来到纽约必应竞技场观看真正的钢拳冠军争霸赛！
Welcome to New York's Bing Arena and the Real Steel Championship Bout.
Tim，就是这样比赛 我们从来没想过会看到
Tim, it's the fight we never thought we'd see.
Zeus，独孤求败的WRB冠军
Zeus, the undefeated WRB champion,
对阵败犬，明日之星Atom.
against the underdog, rising star Atom.
冠军经理人已经同意将这场比赛
The champ's handlers have agreed to fight
放到知名联盟机器人争霸赛的场外
outside the circle of well-known League bots,
决定给观众一个近距离的直观全景！
and have decided to give the people a true David versus Goliath spectacle.
Tim，帮我理理清楚 冠军者Zeus是不是脑子不正常了？
Now, Tim, help me out on this. Has the Zeus camp lost their mind?
最有名，伟大的机器人拳击手
The greatest robot boxer of all time
要和一个G-2级别，叫Atom的同场竞技？
gives a shot at the belt to a G-2 named Atom?
好吧，Herb，如果你去问Tak Mashido，Zeus的团队所有人都疯了
Well, Herb, if you ask Tak Mashido, Team Zeus has lost their minds.
别看他入场时候，酷劲十足
Now, he may look cool as he enters the arena,
但是他弱不禁风的样子对这样的比赛简直就是轻视
but he has made no bones about his disdain for this matchup.
本周早些时候我们的摄像师想要拍摄他
Our cameras tried to catch up with him earlier this week.
看看这些片段，Mashido都忍不住要停下来对媒体说
Look at this clip. Mashido wouldn't even stop to talk to the press,
这场比赛对他的机器人来说简直就是一种羞辱
referring only to this fight as an insult to his creation.
现在，Max Kenton，Atom的训练师做的不仅仅是挑战Zeus
Now, Max Kenton, Atom's trainer, did more than just challenge Zeus.
他是当着媒体的面做出的挑战
He did so publicly.
他的挑战成为了冠军的毒瘤和噩梦
The challenge went viral and created a PR nightmare for the champ.
此处不语评论，我觉得Zeus的团队很清楚他们在做什么
No argument there. And I think the Zeus camp knows exactly what they're doing.
但是他们就是这么做了
That they do. Come on.
接受一个无名小卒的挑战
Giving a shot at the belt to a nobody from nowhere.
这个“垃圾场选手”如果你愿意这么叫 这就是个市场噱头
This "junkyard dog," if you will. That's a marketing stunt.
从涌动的人潮可以看出来，这个噱头很有效
And judging from this crowd, that stunt is working.
我们赢不了，不是么
We can't win, can we?
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
当挑战者进入竞技场时
As the challenger makes his way into the arena,
你们能听到如海潮般的尖叫声
you can hear the surge of excitement.
Atom也来到了WRB的场地，带着强烈的
Atom has arrived onto the WRB scene with a vengeance,
称之为人性的态度，
using a style, some would call it human-like,
这在机器人争霸赛中从没有过
that bot fighting has rarely seen.
Atom和他的小号训练者走进了场地
Atom and his pint-size trainer step into the ring
看Farra Lemkova的脸上表情说明了一切
and the look on Farra Lemkova's face says it all.
欢迎来到大人的世界，小孩子们！
Welcome to the bigs, junior!
我以1赔5的比例压Atom挺不过第一轮
I'm giving one-to-five odds that Atom don't make it out the first round.
谁想来下注
Who wants some?
我来押注
I'll take some of that action.
Hey, there! I'll take some of that action.
怎么样了伙计？
How's it going... partner?
伙计？
Partner?
太好了。十万怎么样？ 有意思么？
That's great. How about a hundred K? Is that funny?
十万赌Atom见不到第二轮
Hundred K says Atom doesn't see round two.
你就这样到处宣传？
You carrying around that kind of scratch?
是啊 十万？
- Yeah. - Hundred K?
你给我记住 101节，C排
Tell you what. Remember section 101, row C,
你去把我的钱带到我的座位这里来
and you can bring me my money right to my seat.
101，C排？十万？
101, row C? Hundred K?
你说的没错，homey
You heard me, homey.
对吧？
- Homey? - Right? homey？
伙计！
Homeboy!
好吧，再见，posse
All right. Peace out, posse.
快，亲爱的，我们走
Come on, sugar. Let's go.
永远不会被击倒 比赛开始！
- Never beaten. - It's showtime!
从不被威胁
Never threatened.
拳击场之王
The king of the ring,
机器人的统治者！
the ruler of robots!
向伟大的Zeus致敬！
Bow down to the mighty Zeus!
哦，我靠！
Oh, shit!
太棒了
That was awesome.
快，我们走
Come on, let's go.
女士们，先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
本次世界机器人拳击争霸赛
in a bout scheduled for five rounds
共计五轮
for the World Robot Boxing Championship,
在我右手边的是挑战者，Atom!
in the corner to my right, the challenger, Atom!
炫耀下吧！
Showboat!
在我左手边的是
And in the corner to my left,
全世界以及另外的可知或不可知的世界里
the undeniable champion of this universe
不可否认的世界冠军
and any other universe known or unknown,
伟大的Zeus!
the mighty Zeus!
女士们，先生们 你们准备好
And now, ladies and gentlemen, are you ready
观看真正的钢拳比赛了么？！
for Real Steel!
这就是你们想要看到的！
This is what it's all about!
开始铃声响了 比赛正式开始
There's the starting bell and we are underway.
机器人们从各自的角落登台
The bots emerge from their corners.
Zeus佯攻了一下Atom,他已经要倒了
Zeus decks Atom, and he is already down.
站稳了！
On your feet!
看起来今天我们可能需要另外一个Zeus急救了
Looks like we are in for another Zeus clinic.
裁判Matt Geiger来到场地开始计数
Referee Matt Geiger coming in the ring to start the count.
起来！
Get up!
伏地挺身！站起来了！
Push up! Stand up!
但是看看这个 小机器人又站起来
But look at this. The little bot's back on his feet
又一次迎接来自Zeus狂风骤雨般的打击
to get a second blistering attack from Zeus!
不到10秒钟的时间Atom又一次倒下了
Atom is down for the second time in less than ten seconds.
他太强了！ 那才是我的好家伙！
- He's too strong! - That's my boy right there!
站起来投入比赛！
Get up and get in the game!
快，不要啊，求你快起来！Atom 求你了
Come on! No, please Atom, get up! Please!
起来！起来！起来！
Get up! Get up! Get up!
又一次 挑战者站了起来！
Once again, the challenger finds his feet!
向后倒去！
Lean back!
Atom 被连续袭来的拳头打到了角落里！
Atom's getting pummeled into the corner!
快离开那儿！ 移动！
- Get out of there! - Move!
一次毁灭性的内侧拳
A demolishing inside shot.
把手举起来！
Get your hands up!
手举起来！
Hands up!
把那个小机器人打烂！
Crush that little can!
从角落里出来！
Get out of the corner!
Kenton拼命的命令他的机器人离开那个死角
Kenton desperately trying to command his robot out of that suicide corner.
把你的脚弄到下面去！
Get your feet under you!
晚上好，夹板机器人！
Good night, sparring bot!
这也许会耗费Zeus更长的时间，但是他又一次做到了！
It might have taken Zeus a bit longer, but he's done it again!
Atom 第三次也许是今晚的最后一次倒地！
Atom is down for the third and possibly final time tonight.
起来！ 二！
- Stand up! - Two!
三！
Three!
Atom ，起来！
Atom, get up!
起来，Atom 起来，Atom
- Get up, Atom. - Get up, Atom.
六！七！ 起来！
- Six! Seven! - Get up!
八！九！
Eight! Nine!
我简直不能相信！无论多困难，这个小机器人又一次的站起来了
I don't believe this! Against all odds, this little bot is on his feet again.
加油Atom ！
Come on, Atom!
他过不了这关的！
He can't survive this!
加油Charlie! 右手上勾拳！
- Come on, Charlie! - Right uppercut!
Atom打出了一记重击！
Atom has landed a punch!
Zeus被突如其来的打得他原地转了一圈的上勾拳吓到了！
Zeus is stunned as he reels back from an uppercut that he never saw coming!
继续向前！
Advance!
后退，右手反击！
Fade back, counter right!
右边双手交叉！右边双手交叉！ 右边双手交叉！左边勾拳！
Right cross! Right cross! Right cross! Left hook!
继续！加油！ 打倒他！
- Let's go! Come on! - Take him down!
在Zeus统治的拳击场里，从来没有遇到过
For the first time in his dominant run,
这样一位不轻言放弃的机器人选手！
Zeus has met a bot who simply won't back down!
观众近乎疯狂！ Zeus使出了浑身招数
The crowd is going nuts! Zeus gives it everything he's got
但是距离第一节比赛只剩下15秒的时间了！
as we reach the last 15 seconds of round one!
Zeus将Atom逼到角里，用双拳重击两次！
Zeus corners Atom, going double duty with both fists!
各位观众朋友，此时此刻，钟声响起了！
Downtown, uptown, as the clock winds down!
举起手来，下巴掉下来 保持低位，保持低位！
- Hands up, chin down. - Stay low, stay low!
只剩下5秒时间，冠军使出了必杀技！
Only five seconds left, as here comes that piston-packed right of the champ!
钟声想起来了，不敢相信 不管怎样Atom坚持下来了！
There's the bell! I don't believe it. Somehow Atom has survived.
我们还有第二轮，观众们都异常兴奋！
We will have a second round. And the crowd here is thrilled!
他做到了！哦也！Corner!
He made it! Yeah! Corner!
我们要离开这儿 我们要立刻离开这儿！
We got to get out of here. We got to get out of here now!
我们要这样做，快！
We got to go this way. Come on!
好吧，你坐下
OK, you sit down.
出发吧，伙计 好吧
- Let's go, homey. - All right.
我会回来找你的，亲爱的
I'll be back for you, baby.
把你的手放开！
Get your hands off me!
两边的团队成员都在迅速的修整机器人
Both corners furiously working on their bots.
今晚来到这儿的观众都期待一张屠杀
This crowd came here tonight expecting a massacre,
但是他们看到的却是一场战斗！
but instead they're getting a war!
你懂了？ 是的
- You got it? - Yeah.
好吧，出发吧
All right. Here we go.
发生了什么？
What is happening?
他已经完全考虑到了所有意外的可能，他会没事的
He is fully prepared for all possible contingencies. He will be fine.
接下来怎么样？
What next?
第二轮
Round two.
第二轮开始， 难以置信的挑战者，Atom,
Round two kicks off, and incredibly the challenger, Atom,
正逼得这位冠军为了他的钱而战
is giving the champ a run for his money.
Zeus将小个子机器人像垃圾桶一样甩过了场地！
Zeus tosses the smaller bot across the ring like a tin can!
Kenton操作的机器人三连击直接击中了冠军的头部！
Kenton working his bot with a trifecta of straight rights to the champ's dome!
面对面对峙，发出了刺耳的撞击声！
Toe-to-toe they stand, trading deafening blows!
不管corner使用的是什么战术，都没有起到作用！
Whatever strategy either corner had cooked up has been destroyed!
针尖对麦芒，招招到肉的战斗
Metal bashing metal. Steel smashing steel.
这才是一场大战！
This is a brawl!
观众们欢呼雀跃，看着两台机器猛兽互相性命！
The crowd is on their feet, watching two machines driven to kill each other!
一定要有些付出，的确如此！
Something has to give, and it does!
Atom又一次倒下了！
Atom goes down again!
看来今晚表现抢眼的垃圾场败犬的表演要结束了！
Lights out for the junkyard dog who put on a heck of a show here tonight!
但是还没有结束， Atom站起来了
And yet again, Atom rises up.
Kenton一定是将自己的战斗不息的坚强意志传输给了这台机器人！
Kenton must have hardwired this bot with the will to go on!
第四轮已经过半，Zeus希望立刻结束这场比赛
Midway through round four, and Zeus is looking to end this thing right now.
冠军孤注一掷，用力敲破锁扣装置！
The champ is holding nothing back as he cracks open the hurt locker!
Atom 在场地中跌跌撞撞，很明显迷失了方向感！
Atom is stumbling around the ring, apparently disoriented and dazed!
举起手来！ 发生了什么？
- Hands up! - What's going on?
我觉得声音识别系统坏了！ 他没有反应！
I think the voice recog is shot! He's not responding!
Zeus找到了另外一个暴力装置，直捣Atom的腹部
Zeus has found yet another gear of violence, drilling Atom's midsection.
不！停下！做点什么！
No! Stop! Do something!
他听不到我！
He can't hear me!
但是铃声在响，又一次这个小机器人让全世界震惊了！
But the bell sounds, and once again this little robot has stunned the world!
我们完蛋了Max!他听不到我 这就是谋杀，我们已经够了
We're done, Max! He can't hear me. This is murder. We've had enough.
我破坏了声音识别系统 他听不到我！
- I'm disabling the voice recognition. - He can't hear me!
是的，但是他能看到你！ 什么？
- Yes, but he can see you! - What?
我把他设置成影子模式 告诉他该怎么做
I'm putting him in shadow mode. Show him what to do.
不用声音识别，他会移动的更快
Without the voice recognition, he'll move even faster!
不可能，不可能！
No way. No way!
看看他们，他们吓坏了！
Look at them. They are freaking out!
有钱的小女孩正在那边帮他找一个新的!
Rich girl is ripping him a new one over there!
你知道为什么么？ 因为他们害怕了
Do you know why? Because they're scared.
因为Atom能做到其他机器人不能做的事情
Because Atom can do things no other bot has ever done.
但是我做不到 是的，你能
- But I can't do it! - Yes, you can.
我不能 是的，你能
- I can't. - Yes, you can.
告诉他还怎么做 你不用在最后一轮出击
Show him what to do. You have to fight the last round.
别问我，别这样
Don't ask me. Don't.
Charlie...求你了
Charlie... please. I beg you.
你用这些眼睛骗我呢啊？
Are you kidding me with those eyes?
我靠！
Damn it!
是的！
Yes!
不能相信我要这么做
I can't believe I'm doing this.
我知道你在那儿！我不确定你能不能懂我的意思
I know you're in there! I'm not sure if you're getting this or what,
但是我知道你在那儿！
but I know you're in there!
Kenton.上还是不上？ 上，给我一分钟
- Kenton. In or out? - In. Give me a minute.
我知道你听不到我 但是你能看到我，看着我！
I know you can't hear me, but you can see me, so watch me!
看着...我
Watch... me.
你知道你在和一个机器人说话 我知道，闭嘴
- You know you're talking to a robot. - I know. Shut up.
看着我
Watch me.
今天晚上是一场世纪大战
An epic battle being waged here tonight,
五轮半都已经过去了
as the fifth and final round gets underway.
加油，Atom!
Come on, Atom!
等一下，你们看到了没？
Wait a second. Are you seeing this?
Charlie Kenton在场地外在做空击练习
Charlie Kenton is shadowboxing just outside the ring!
看起来Atom有影子功能
It looks like Atom has a shadow function.
也就是说Charlie Kenton
So, basically, that means Charlie Kenton
在最后一轮用这种方式对抗Zeus.
is fighting the last round of this fight against Zeus.
看起来没什么帮助，因为Atom又一次靠在了防护绳上
It doesn't seem to help, because Atom is backed up against the ropes again.
帮他！反击！
Help him! Fight back!
还不行
Not yet.
正当Zeus用重锤砸下来时，Tak Mashido亲自指挥
Tak Mashido supervising personally as Zeus hammers down,
希望一次性解决战斗
furiously trying to end this thing once and for all.
我要告诉你们，朋友们，冠军看起来累了
I got to tell you, folks, the champ looks tired.
这个机器人看起来有点发虚
This robot seems to be running on empty.
我不敢相信 Atom在嘲弄Zeus
I don't believe it. Atom is taunting Zeus.
转到加速！ 他希望得到更多！
- Switch to turbo! - He's actually asking for more.
求你做点事！
Please do something!
还不行 对的，Charlie，还不到时候
- Not yet. - That's right, Charlie. Not yet.
氮气活塞，现在！
Nitrous pistons, now!
他坚持不了多久！
He's not going to last much longer!
反击！ 还不行
- Fight back! - Not yet.
等等！
Hang in there!
Atom被 Zeus的氮气燃料机枪打的全身是洞！
Atom is riddled with the nitrous-fueled Gatling guns of Zeus's blows!
Atom! Atom! Atom! Atom! Atom! Atom! Atom! Atom!
等他出来，等他出来！还不行！
Wait him out, wait him out! Not yet!
Zeus在减速！
Zeus is slowing down!
冠军的燃料内核很明显耗尽了
The champ's power core is clearly depleted.
Charlie，求你了！
Charlie, please!
嘿，孩子
Hey, kid.
现在 现在!
- Now. - Now!
瞄准他！
Get in there!
打掉那个混蛋！把他炸开！
Knock that little bitch! Bust him open!
对！就这样！
Yeah! That's right!
做点什么！
Do something!
移动啊！
Move!
重置，恢复手动操作
Override. Switching to manual.
一个令人震惊的动作，Tak Mashido亲自手动操作他的机器人！
In a shocking move, Tak Mashido is manually operating his robot personally!
操纵身体！靠近他！ 打倒他，Atom!
- Work the body! Get inside him! - Get him, Atom!
看看这个！冠军正在竭尽全力的想要站起来
Look at this! The champ is trying desperately to stay on his feet,
但是Kenton没有停下来，一拳接一拳重重的打在他的身上！
but Kenton is relentless, landing blow after blow after blow to the body!
左！右！左！右！
Left! Right! Left! Right!
Atom使出了一击上勾拳！Zeus倒下了！
A huge uppercut by Atom! Zeus is down!
这个小机器人今晚发挥了全部潜力
This little bot has dug deep here tonight
展现了近乎令人窒息的一面！
and shown something damn near heart!
一，二，三，
One, two, three,
四，五，六，七...
four, five, six, seven...
好样的！
He's good!
Zeus站起来了，但是Kenton操纵Atom又一次压在他身上
Zeus gets to his feet, but Kenton has Atom on him again,
一拳接一拳的不停痛击！
landing punch after punch!
Tak Mashido和他的超级机器人没有了反应
Tak Mashido and his super bot have no answer.
Zeus卡住Atom的左臂，但是Kenton却不畏惧！
Zeus pins Atom's left arm, but Kenton is undaunted!
一切就到此为止，伙计们！
It all comes down to this, folks!
摔他，Charlie！现在！
Drop him, Charlie! Now!
Kenton正要把冠军重摔在地... 不！此刻铃声响了！
- Kenton is about to drop the champ... - No! There's the bell!
Zeus被铃声救了一命！
Zeus is saved by the bell!
太神奇了，我们来看裁判们的板子！
Amazingly, we will go to the judges' cards!
女士们先生们，五轮过后
Ladies and gentlemen, after five rounds,
我们来看一下裁判们的分数牌
we go to the judges' scorecards.
一号裁判 得分47-48
Judge Number One scores the fight 47-48.
二号裁判 得分48-46
Judge Number Two scores the fight 48-46.
三号裁判 得分47-46,
And Judge Number Three scores the fight 47-46,
所以获胜者依然是世界机器人拳击争霸赛总冠军，
for the winner and still World Robot Boxing champion,
Zeus! Zeus!
Farra Lemkova, Farra Lemkova,
今晚你得到的比预期的要多好多
you got way more than you bargained for tonight.
有些人会说你的机器人赢了口碑却输了比赛
Some would say that your bot won the decision but lost the fight.
她看起来很生气
She looks pissed.
比我们想想的花的时间要长
It took a little longer than we thought,
但是结果不出所料
but the result is as expected.
我们赢了，Zeus依然无人可敌
We won. Zeus is still undefeated.
你的机器人今天晚上受尽侮辱
Any comment on the absolutely humiliating near loss
还差点失败，你就没什么好评论的？
your bot suffered tonight?
没有 毫无评论
- Nothing. - No comment.
Max,Max 在哪儿？
Max. Where's Max?
他在这儿Max
There he is. Max.
他们已经开始叫你的机器人“人民冠军”了
They're already calling your bot "the people's champion."
关于此你有什么看法？
What do you say to that?
人民冠军？
People's champion?
听起来还不赖
Sounds pretty good to me.
爸爸？爸爸！
Dad? Dad!
爸爸！
Dad!
我真的想让你知道...
I really want you to know...
不，你必须知道
No, I need you to know.
别担心
Don't worry.
你的秘密我会保守的
Your secret's safe with me.
在这儿等着，在这儿等着
Wait here. Wait here.
好的！
Yes!
V游网字幕组荣誉出品  如有不当之处还请见谅
感谢翻译者 叮,spawnix,vootoo
最新大片下载尽在www.verypsp.com